好的，完成啦。看看我们结果如何。如果你
All right, you're done. Let's look at the solution. If you
猜我们要把代码加入在Sunshine sync adapter的里面
guessed that we were going add this code to Sunshine sync adapter,
你可是再对不过了。我们就是要把代码加在那里面，
you would've been right. We're actually going to place the code right
因为这里我们知道上次我们成功的放进代码的地方。
here, because this is where we know we've done a successful insert.
所以现在要做什么呢？我们从日历这个对象
So what do we do? So we start off with the
当前的一天开始着手。然后我们在昨天的日期这个数据上
calendar object, for the current day. Then we add negative 1 to
加入一个-1的值。最后我们把数据放进
the date which means it points to yesterday. Finally, we convert
数据库里。我们再做一个请求，把所有日期小于或等于
that into a database-friendly string. And then we do a query to
昨天的值的都删除掉。
delete everything less than or equal to that day.
搞定，打扫卫生，清理垃圾总是好的。
Done. It's always good to clean up after yourself.